baaz.com 2016-04-04

# None

This document discloses the privacy practices for [www.Baaz.com](https://www.baaz.com/) (“Site”), a website owned and operated by Baaz, Inc. ("Baaz"). As part of the normal operation of Baaz services, we collect and, in some cases, disclose information about you. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you, how Baaz may use such information, and what may happen to that information. By accepting the Terms of Service, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Baaz Terms of Use Agreement.

### _Minors_

If you are a minor (under the age of 18), you can use this service only [in conjunction with / with the consent and under the supervision of] your parents or legal guardians. If you are a minor, please do not submit any personal information to this website. IF YOU ARE YOUNGER THAN 13 YEARS, PLEASE DO NOT USE BAAZ OR ANY OF ITS SERVICES FOR ANY PURPOSE.

### _Information We Collect_

Your Registration Information. To fully use our services, you will need to register using our online registration form, where you will be required to provide us with your contact information and certain other personal information, namely, your first and last name, email, gender and date of birth.

Your Usage of Our Site. We automatically track certain information about you based upon your use of our Site. We use this information to conduct internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your IP address.

Cookies. In addition, we use "cookies" on certain pages of our site. Cookies are small files that can be used to track a user's steps or automatically generate a user's password. Some features of our website may only be available through the use of a cookie. Among other things, cookies allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information which is targeted to your interests. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our Site. Most, but not all, cookies are automatically deleted at the end of a session. You may decline our cookies if your browser permits, although your use of the Site may then be restricted (as noted above).

Your Posts. If you choose to post messages on our Site, we will collect such information about you as you may choose to disclose pursuant to your activities on the Site.

Your Correspondence. If you send us e-mails, letters or other personal correspondence, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

Your Credit Account. If you establish a credit account with us, we collect some additional information, including billing address, credit card number and credit card expiration date and tracking information from checks or money orders.

### _Our Use of Your Information_

Promotional Use. We use personal information about you to enhance our marketing and promotional efforts, and to improve our content and services. We may also use your information to deliver to you advertisements, new services and promotions, and other information to you that is targeted to your interests. You will have the ability to not receive such advertisements, promotions, notices and information by changing your options on your account settings page.

Administrative Notices, etc. We may use your e-mail address to contact you regarding administrative notices, new product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. If you do not wish to receive these communications, you may opt out of receiving these notices on your account settings page.

Billing and Support. If you open a credit account with our website, we may use your address and billing information to bill you and provide associated support.

Dispute Resolution. We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of Service.

### _Our Disclosure to Third Parties_

We use practices that are consistent with standards in our industry to protect your privacy. We cannot, however, promise that your personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private. For example, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications on our Site. We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. The following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

Law Enforcement. We may disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

Advertisers. We disclose aggregate information about our users to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, we do not disclose any personally identifying information to any of these entities.

Baaz Site. Throughout the Site, you are identified by your User ID. While your email address is not disclosed automatically by us anywhere through the Site, if you choose to do so we take no responsibility over unsolicited emails you may receive. Although our pages are coded with robot exclusion headers, others may attempt to automatically collect your e-mail address from our Site. We describe how to change your User ID in your user settings. Even if your User ID is not your e-mail address, your User ID can be used to identify you and your activities throughout the Site. Based on the privacy options you choose for public disclosure, other people can see your activities on the Site, including any of your comments and postings on the Site.

Third Party Suppliers. We may use third party suppliers to assist us in providing the services available on an outside website. Whenever a third party supplier desires to collect information about you, you will be notified of the involvement of the third party supplier, and you will never be required to disclose any information to the third party supplier. We impose contractual restrictions on the use by our third party suppliers of information concerning you, and we do not permit third party suppliers to sell your information to other third parties.

Use Limited to Site-Related Communications. Because of the nature of the services offered on Baaz, Baaz allows you to access other users' contact information. You may use such information only for Baaz-related communications. Baaz-related communication expressly excludes unsolicited commercial messages. In all cases, you must give users an opportunity to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances can you disclose personally identifiable information about another user to any third party without our consent and the consent of such other user after adequate disclosure by you to such other user. Note that law enforcement personnel, are given different rights with respect to information they access.

No Spam. Baaz and our users do not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you are not licensed to add a Baaz user to your mail list (e-mail or physical mail) without their express consent after adequate disclosure.

### _Disclosures You Make to Third Parties_

Baaz does not control the privacy policies of third parties. When you disclose information to third parties on Baaz (or any other website) about yourself, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of that third party. It is your responsibility to find out about the privacy policy of any such third parties.

### _Changes to Privacy Policy_

Baaz reserves the right at any time to make changes, modifications, alterations and/or additions to this Privacy Policy. Baaz will notify you of any changes to this Privacy Policy by providing you with notice of such changes at your email address that you provided the Site as your primary contact information.

### _Special Provisions_

The following provisions apply to users and non-users who interact with Baaz outside the United States:

  1. You consent to having your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.
  2. If you are located in a country embargoed by the United States, or are on the U.S. Treasury Department's list of Specially Designated Nationals you will not engage in commercial activities on Baaz (such as advertising or payments) or operate a Platform application or website. You will not use Baaz if you are prohibited from receiving products, services, or software originating from the United States.
  3. You should be aware that Baaz acts as an intermediary between our users and the various platforms and Third-Party Apps. In some cases, the information published on Baaz which is on the various platforms or Third-Party Apps is not within Baaz custody or control. Any content shared by you through these platforms or Third-Party Apps that is not under the control or custody of Baaz will be accessible to third parties or possibly the public, as this content is now under the control of the operators of the Supported Platforms and/or the Third-Party Apps.

### _Questions about Privacy Policy_

If you have any questions regarding the Baaz Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@baaz.com](mailto:info@Baaz.com).
